[{
        "question": "What is 3 x 4?",
        "answer": "12",
        "qType": "text",
        "aType": "text"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is 5 x 6?",
        "answer": "30",
        "qType": "text",
        "aType": "text"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is 7 x 8?",
        "answer": "56",
        "qType": "text",
        "aType": "text"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is 9 x 3?",
        "answer": "27",
        "qType": "text",
        "aType": "text"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is 10 x 4?",
        "answer": "40",
        "qType": "text",
        "aType": "text"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is 2 x 8?",
        "answer": "16",
        "qType": "text",
        "aType": "text"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is 5 x 9?",
        "answer": "45",
        "qType": "text",
        "aType": "text"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is 6 x 7?",
        "answer": "42",
        "qType": "text",
        "aType": "text"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is 7 x 5?",
        "answer": "35",
        "qType": "text",
        "aType": "text"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is 10 x 8?",
        "answer": "80",
        "qType": "text",
        "aType": "text"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is 4 x 7?",
        "answer": "28",
        "qType": "text",
        "aType": "text"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is 8 x 5?",
        "answer": "40",
        "qType": "text",
        "aType": "text"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is 3 x 6?",
        "answer": "18",
        "qType": "text",
        "aType": "text"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is 9 x 2?",
        "answer": "18",
        "qType": "text",
        "aType": "text"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is 10 x 3?",
        "answer": "30",
        "qType": "text",
        "aType": "text"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is 2 x 9?",
        "answer": "18",
        "qType": "text",
        "aType": "text"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is 6 x 4?",
        "answer": "24",
        "qType": "text",
        "aType": "text"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is 5 x 8?",
        "answer": "40",
        "qType": "text",
        "aType": "text"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is 7 x 3?",
        "answer": "21",
        "qType": "text",
        "aType": "text"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is 10 x 2?",
        "answer": "20",
        "qType": "text",
        "aType": "text"
    }
]